{
  "questions":
  [
    {
      "question": "It's the closest star to the Sun",
      "answers": [
        "Sirius",
        "Pleiades",
        "Alpha Centauri",
        "Polaris"
      ],
      "answerindex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "This is the name for space rocks that survive the fall to Earth's surface",
      "answers": [
        "Asteroid",
        "Comet",
        "Spaceball",
        "Meteorite"
      ],
      "answerindex": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Scientists have high hopes for this watery moon of Jupiter",
      "answers": [
        "Titan",
        "Europa",
        "Ganymede",
        "Pluto"
      ],
      "answerindex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "At first his idea that the earth revolved around the sun caused quite a fuss",
      "answers": [
        "Kepler",
        "Galileo",
        "Copernicus",
        "Newton"
      ],
      "answerindex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Stars are born from these gassy clouds",
      "answers": [
        "Asteroid belts",
        "Galaxies",
        "Nebulae",
        "Black holes"
      ],
      "answerindex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "This celestial object emits bright beams of light as it spins rapidly, probably lending it its name",
      "answers": [
        "Meteor",
        "Pulsar",
        "Red dwarf",
        "Super nova"
      ],
      "answerindex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Massive objects like stars and black holes might form one of these hot spirals around it",
      "answers": [
        "Accretion disk",
        "Asteroid belt",
        "Lava loop",
        "Galaxy"
      ],
      "answerindex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "This outermost part of the sun's atmosphere is very hard to see, except during a solar eclipse",
      "answers": [
        "Crown",
        "Nucleus",
        "Stratosphere",
        "Corona"
      ],
      "answerindex": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Comet tails always appear to be facing this way, due to the evaporation of gas and water",
      "answers": [
        "Towards the sun",
        "Away from the sun",
        "Backwards",
        "Away from earth"
      ],
      "answerindex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "This water serpent is the largest constellation in the sky",
      "answers": [
        "Aquarius",
        "Pisces",
        "Hydra",
        "Leo"
      ],
      "answerindex": 2
    }
  ]
}